[{"question":"","answer":[]},{"question":"If we are lucky, we ___ to see the northern lights tonight.","answer":["were able","is going to able","are able"]},{"question":"She ___ a movie with us if she gets paid this afternoon.","answer":["will went"]},{"question":"My father will call me after he ___ at his hotel.","answer":["is going to check in"]},{"question":"Which conditional form does the sentence use?If she wants to be in shape, she has to exercise regularly.","answer":["first conditional"]},{"question":"If she gets eight hours of sleep, she usually ___ alert.","answer":["is feeling alert","has felt"]},{"question":"Nancy ___ better as soon as she has a cup of black tea.","answer":["will feeling","will feels"]},{"question":"If Joe ___ the book, I will lend it to him.","answer":["has reads","is read","haven’t read"]},{"question":"As soon as they ___ the English exam, they will go to America.","answer":["will pass","passed","are passing"]},{"question":"Which conditional form does the sentence use?Plants die if you don’t water them.","answer":["first conditional"]},{"question":"Which conditional form does the sentence use?If the temperature drops to 0°, water freezes.","answer":["first conditional"]},{"question":"I will get some gas now ___ the price goes up later.","answer":["after","for"]},{"question":"Which conditional form does the sentence use?My sister will stay at a friend’s house if she finishes work late.","answer":["zero conditional"]},{"question":"My mother won’t give me any pocket money unless I ___ my room weekly.","answer":["am to clean","cleaned"]},{"question":"Sophie will buy some souvenirs before she ___ Japan.","answer":["left"]},{"question":"You ___ if you don’t wear a mask in public.","answer":["fine","can fine"]}]